[Soft instrumental music]
[Música instrumental suave]
[Renata] Okay... where do I even start?
[Renata] Bueno... ¿por dónde empiezo?
[Voice Access] Mm-hm. Take your time. What are you trying to get ready for?
[Voice Access] Mm-hm. Tómate tu tiempo. ¿Para qué te estás preparando?
[Renata] I need help with my diabetes, and— actually, I don't need advice. I need to know where to go.
[Renata] Necesito ayuda con mi diabetes y... no busco consejos. Necesito saber adónde ir.
[Voice Access] Got it. You're looking for a place to begin, not medical advice.
[Voice Access] Entiendo. Buscas un punto de partida, no orientación médica.
[Renata] Exactly. And it has to be close. I don't drive.
[Renata] Exacto. Y tiene que estar cerca. No conduzco.
[Voice Access] Okay. May I use your county and preferred language to narrow the options?
[Voice Access] De acuerdo. ¿Puedo usar tu condado y el idioma que prefieres para limitar las opciones?
[Renata] Yes. Delaware County. English is fine.
[Renata] Sí. Condado de Delaware. Prefiero español.
[Voice Access] Thanks. I’ll bring your county, language, transportation, and follow-up details together, then show you the request so you can review—
[Voice Access] Gracias. Reuniré los datos del condado, idioma, transporte y seguimiento, y luego te mostraré la solicitud para que puedas revisar—
[Renata] Wait—does that mean you found a provider?
[Renata] Espera, ¿eso significa que encontraste un proveedor?
[Voice Access] No. I haven't matched you to a provider. SozoRock doesn't diagnose, treat, or prescribe. Licensed care stays with licensed professionals.
[Voice Access] No. No te he asignado un proveedor. SozoRock no diagnostica, trata ni receta. La atención clínica permanece con profesionales autorizados.
[Renata] Okay. Show me what the request needs.
[Renata] Bien. Muéstrame la solicitud.
[Voice Access] County, language, transport, follow-up. Tap or type to confirm.
[Voice Access] Condado, idioma, transporte y seguimiento. Revisa y confirma por toque o texto.
[Narrator] One natural conversation. One clearer next step.
[Narrador] Una conversación natural. Un próximo paso más claro.
[Narrator] SozoRock Health. A clearer path to care that already exists.
[Narrador] SozoRock Health. Un camino más claro hacia la atención que ya existe.